<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <Crashlanded.label>Crashlanded</Crashlanded.label>
  <Crashlanded.description>The three of you awake in your cryptosleep sarcophagi to the sound of sirens and ripping metal. You barely get to the escape pods before the ship is torn apart. Some time later, you land on this unknown rimworld.</Crashlanded.description>
  <Crashlanded.scenario.name>Crashlanded</Crashlanded.scenario.name>
  <Crashlanded.scenario.summary>Three crashlanded survivors - the classic RimWorld experience.</Crashlanded.scenario.summary>
  <Crashlanded.scenario.description>The three of you awake in your cryptosleep sarcophagi to the sound of sirens and ripping metal. You barely get to the escape pods before the ship is torn apart. Some time later, you land on this unknown rimworld.</Crashlanded.scenario.description>

  <LostTribe.label>Lost Tribe</LostTribe.label>
  <LostTribe.description>Your tribe was destroyed by the great blood machines sent by the gods. Five of you managed to escape. Now, it's time to build up a new home.\n\nNote: Since you'll start poor and research slowly, this is a difficult scenario.</LostTribe.description>
  <LostTribe.scenario.name>Lost Tribe</LostTribe.scenario.name>
  <LostTribe.scenario.summary>Five lost tribespeople attempt to rebuild. Difficult.</LostTribe.scenario.summary>
  <LostTribe.scenario.description>Your tribe was destroyed by the great blood machines sent by the gods. Five of you managed to escape. Now, it's time to build up a new home.\n\nNote: Since you'll start poor and research slowly, this is a difficult scenario.</LostTribe.scenario.description>
  <LostTribe.scenario.parts.14.text>The gods were very angry. The blood machines came at night. They swept through your village, cutting and burning your people with their blades and devil-fire.\n\nOnly a few of you escaped. Now, after a harrowing journey on foot, with no close friends to turn to, you must build a new home in the wilderness, like your ancestors did.</LostTribe.scenario.parts.14.text>

  <TheRichExplorer.label>The Rich Explorer</TheRichExplorer.label>
  <TheRichExplorer.description>People called you crazy for leaving your glitterworld home, but you always yearned to explore the stars - outside the neurosimulator. Now you're at the end of your long journey in cryptosleep, landing on an unknown rimworld to see what it's like.\n\nNote: Since your starting character will lack some skills, this is an especially difficult scenario in the early game.</TheRichExplorer.description>
  <TheRichExplorer.scenario.name>The Rich Explorer</TheRichExplorer.scenario.name>
  <TheRichExplorer.scenario.summary>One rich explorer out to experience the universe. Extra difficult.</TheRichExplorer.scenario.summary>
  <TheRichExplorer.scenario.description>People called you crazy for leaving your glitterworld home, but you always yearned to explore the stars - outside the neurosimulator. Now you're at the end of your long journey in cryptosleep, landing on an unknown rimworld to see what it's like.\n\nNote: Since your starting character will lack some skills, this is an especially difficult scenario in the early game.</TheRichExplorer.scenario.description>
  <TheRichExplorer.scenario.parts.12.text>The neurosimulations, holo-games, and free-orgies were never enough for you. You wanted more - the grit and consequence of real life, like they talk about in the history books. You wanted to know what real challenge and consequence feel like.\n\nNow, after a journey of decades in cryptosleep, you're landing on this unknown rimworld. Real consequences await you.</TheRichExplorer.scenario.parts.12.text>


</LanguageData>