<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <OrbitalTradeBeacon.label>orbital trade beacon</OrbitalTradeBeacon.label>
  <OrbitalTradeBeacon.description>Required for orbital trading. You can only sell goods that are near an orbital trade beacon. Can be placed indoors.</OrbitalTradeBeacon.description>

  <CommsConsole.label>comms console</CommsConsole.label>
  <CommsConsole.description>Allows radio contact with remote traders as well as other factions for trade and diplomacy.</CommsConsole.description>

  <FirefoamPopper.label>firefoam popper</FirefoamPopper.label>
  <FirefoamPopper.description>When touched by fire or triggered by hand, this pops and sprays a fire-extinguishing foam in a circular field around itself.</FirefoamPopper.description>
  <FirefoamPopper.comps.1.useLabel>Trigger firefoam popper</FirefoamPopper.comps.1.useLabel>

  <MoisturePump.label>moisture pump</MoisturePump.label>
  <MoisturePump.description>Very slowly removes moisture from nearby terrain, converting marshes or shallow water into dry ground. Does not affect deep water.</MoisturePump.description>

  <GroundPenetratingScanner.label>ground-penetrating scanner</GroundPenetratingScanner.label>
  <GroundPenetratingScanner.description>A downward-facing penetrating radar, combined with sonar and magnetic imagers, allows you to detect (but not identify) minerals buried deep under the surface. Requires a huge amount of electricity.</GroundPenetratingScanner.description>


  <!-- Transport pods -->

  <PodLauncher.label>pod launcher</PodLauncher.label>
  <PodLauncher.description>A fueling port for launching one transport pod. Pod launchers can launch as a group - but the launchers must be placed adjacent to each other.</PodLauncher.description>

  <TransportPod.label>transport pod</TransportPod.label>
  <TransportPod.description>A launchable suborbital-travel cargo pod capable of carrying people, items, or animals. Can be used for transport, surprise attacks, or reinforcing battles.</TransportPod.description>


  <!-- Facilities -->

  <MultiAnalyzer.label>multi-analyzer</MultiAnalyzer.label>
  <MultiAnalyzer.description>Increases research speed. Needs to be placed near hi-tech research bench. One research bench can be linked to only one multi-analyzer.</MultiAnalyzer.description>

  <VitalsMonitor.label>vitals monitor</VitalsMonitor.label>
  <VitalsMonitor.description>Increases patients treatment quality. Needs to be placed adjacent to a medical bed. One medical bed can be linked to only one vitals monitor.</VitalsMonitor.description>

  <ToolCabinet.label>tool cabinet</ToolCabinet.label>
  <ToolCabinet.description>Increases work speed. Needs to be placed near workbench. One workbench can be simultaneously linked to only two tools cabinets.</ToolCabinet.description>


  <!-- Graves -->

  <Grave.label>grave</Grave.label>
  <Grave.description>Place the dead in graves to give them a decent final resting place. Colonists will visit full graves to gain meditative joy.</Grave.description>

  <Sarcophagus.label>sarcophagus</Sarcophagus.label>
  <Sarcophagus.description>An ornamented burial receptacle for the honored dead.</Sarcophagus.description>


  <!-- Cryptosleep caskets -->

  <CryptosleepCasket.label>cryptosleep casket</CryptosleepCasket.label>
  <CryptosleepCasket.description>A self-powered sarcophagus designed to keep a person in a state of suspended animation for many years.</CryptosleepCasket.description>

  <AncientCryptosleepCasket.label>ancient cryptosleep casket</AncientCryptosleepCasket.label>
  <AncientCryptosleepCasket.description>This cryptosleep casket looks like it has been here for a very long time. Who knows what it might contain?</AncientCryptosleepCasket.description>


  <!-- Spots -->

  <MarriageSpot.label>marriage spot</MarriageSpot.label>
  <MarriageSpot.description>Designates a spot where marriage ceremonies will take place. Spectators can watch from either side.</MarriageSpot.description>

  <PartySpot.label>party spot</PartySpot.label>
  <PartySpot.description>Designates a spot where parties will be centered. Parties use an area around the spot.</PartySpot.description>


</LanguageData>