<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Column 1 -->

  <PsychoidBrewing.label>psychoid brewing</PsychoidBrewing.label>
  <PsychoidBrewing.description>Prepare psychoid leaves into a mildly euphoria-inducing and addictive tea.</PsychoidBrewing.description>

  <Pemmican.label>pemmican</Pemmican.label>
  <Pemmican.description>Make pemmican, a preserved mixture of meat and plant matter that doesn't go bad for a long time. Great for traveling.</Pemmican.description>

  <Bedrolls.label>bedrolls</Bedrolls.label>
  <Bedrolls.description>Make bedrolls, easy-to-carry sleeping accomodations.</Bedrolls.description>

  <ComplexFurniture.label>complex furniture</ComplexFurniture.label>
  <ComplexFurniture.description>Build complex furniture like beds, end tables, dining chairs, armchairs, dressers, tool cabinets, billiard tables, and poker tables, vents, sarcophagi, and more.</ComplexFurniture.description>

  <PassiveCooler.label>passive cooler</PassiveCooler.label>
  <PassiveCooler.description>Make passive coolers, to cool indoor spaces without using electricity.</PassiveCooler.description>

  <Stonecutting.label>stonecutting</Stonecutting.label>
  <Stonecutting.description>Cut rock chunks into stone blocks for use in construction. Build beautiful stone tile floors or ugly concrete walkways.</Stonecutting.description>

  <ComplexClothing.label>complex clothing</ComplexClothing.label>
  <ComplexClothing.description>Tailor complicated garments like pants, dusters, and cowboy hats.</ComplexClothing.description>


  <!-- Column 2 -->

  <DrugProduction.label>drug production</DrugProduction.label>
  <DrugProduction.description>Build a drug lab for basic drug synthesis. Further research is required to make specific drugs.</DrugProduction.description>

  <Brewing.label>beer brewing</Brewing.label>
  <Brewing.description>Build a brewery and fermenting vats to transform hops into tasty, tasty beer.</Brewing.description>

  <Devilstrand.label>devilstrand</Devilstrand.label>
  <Devilstrand.description>Plant devilstrand, a slow-growing mushroom that yields an exceptionally tough, heat-resistant plant fiber.</Devilstrand.description>

  <Bridges.label>bridges</Bridges.label>
  <Bridges.description>Build bridges to provide passage over water or construct non-heavy structures on otherwise unbuildable terrain.</Bridges.description>

  <CarpetMaking.label>carpet making</CarpetMaking.label>
  <CarpetMaking.description>Weave beautiful carpets from cloth.</CarpetMaking.description>

  <TreeSowing.label>tree sowing</TreeSowing.label>
  <TreeSowing.description>Sow the local biome's natural trees in your fields.</TreeSowing.description>


  <!-- Column 3+ -->

  <Smithing.label>smithing</Smithing.label>
  <Smithing.description>Build smithies for crafting metal weapons like knives, gladii, and maces. Work metal into clean, beautiful floor tiles.</Smithing.description>

  <RecurveBow.label>recurve bow</RecurveBow.label>
  <RecurveBow.description>Build the recurve bow, an effective and inexpensive ranged weapon.</RecurveBow.description>

  <Electricity.label>electricity</Electricity.label>
  <Electricity.description>Harness the power of electricity for a hundred different tasks.</Electricity.description>


</LanguageData>